Then we have our big student pub Little heart-
-while driven by the student union.
It feels like the students have a secret life.
-Yes.
- Yes, a little so.
As a non-student, it doesn't feel like there are so many students in town.
- No, we stick to our pubs.
- With your community.
So don't get there and ruin.
I think it has to do with campus being outside.
It is not outside town, but it is not in the center-
-Or you have it a little south.
And then it becomes like the bubble we live in ports in that direction.
You come directly from high school-
-And then it is not uncommon to pass all the tests right away.
But it's a completely different thing here.
There are much larger tasks and tentor-
-So you are not really prepared for that kind of test.
But it's totally okay to cog an exam.
You are not suspended and sent home.
You plug in.
Maybe an angry text message from mom saying: now you have not plugged-
-And then you say: No, I haven't.
You must have a green card in golf to get people to record you in Halmstad.
Yeah.
- For us who cog exams, so.
-Thanks.
- Unfortunately, I couldn't stop it.
- No, okay.
The thing is well that I say that you have to value it-
-If you should be diplomatic in saying that was the way it was.
Yes, you might not go out to cog, because you want to party-
-But the possibility.
Has it been so ever that it has been a party, but you have to plug-
-But shit the same -now we drive.
I combine it then.
You bring the book with you then?